const quiz4data = [
    {
      question: "Even though it was raining, they continued ___.",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "playing", isCorrect: false},
        {answer: "to play", isCorrect: false},
        {answer: "both", isCorrect: true},
     ],
      help: 'The verbs begin, cease, start and continue can be followed by either a to-infinitive or an -ing form with little difference in meaning.'
   },
    {
      question: "I'm starting ___ Spanish.",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "to learn", isCorrect: true},
        {answer: "learning", isCorrect: true},
      ],
      help: 'The verbs begin, cease, start and continue can be followed by either a to-infinitive or an -ing form with little difference in meaning. However, with these verbs we normally avoid using two -ing forms, as a repeated pattern can sound awkward.'
   },
    {
      question: "I advised my students ____ more exercises.",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "to take", isCorrect: true},
        {answer: "taking", isCorrect: false}
      ],
      help: 'The verbs "advise" and "encourage" are followed by to-infinitive when there is object and -ing when there is no object.'
   },
    {
      question: "___ is bad for your health.",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "To smoke", isCorrect: false},
        {answer: "Smoking", isCorrect: true},
      ],
      help: 'We use certain verbs +ing at the beginning of a sentence when it`s used as the subject.'
   },
    {
      question: "I know I got the milk, I remember ___ it.",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "to buy", isCorrect: false},
        {answer: "buying", isCorrect: true},
      ],
      help: 'Some verbs are followed by -ing or to + infinitive, but with a difference in meaning. These include: come, mean, regret, remember, stop, go on. As a very general rule we use -ing form when the action of the verb has already been done and to + infinitive when its not.'
   },
    {
      question: "Daniel left the job without ____ anything to me.",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "to say", isCorrect: false},
        {answer: "saying", isCorrect: true},
      ],
      help: 'After a preposition we use -ing form.'
   },
    {
      question: "I regret ___ you that your student loan has been rejected.",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "informing", isCorrect: false},
        {answer: "to inform", isCorrect: true},
      ],
      help: 'I am about to do something I am not happy about.'
   },
    {
      question: "",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "", isCorrect: false},
        {answer: "", isCorrect: true},
      ],
      help: ''
   },
    {
      question: "Yesterday they stole my neighbor's house but not mine, because I remembered ___ the door.",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "locking", isCorrect: false},
        {answer: "to lock", isCorrect: true},
      ],
      help: '"I remembered that I had to lock it, and so I locked it."'
   },
    {
      question: "",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "", isCorrect: false},
        {answer: "", isCorrect: true},
      ],
      help: ''
   },
    {
      question: "",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "", isCorrect: false},
        {answer: "", isCorrect: true},
      ],
      help: ''
   },
    {
      question: "",
      answersList: [
        {answer: "", isCorrect: false},
        {answer: "", isCorrect: true},
      ],
      help: ''
   }
  ]
export default quiz4data
